ILGWU. New York Cloak Joint Board records 5780/020
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Administrative departments of the Cloak Joint Board that are represented includes: the reports of the Cloak and Suit Department within the Joint Board; the Health and Welfare Fund and its predecessor the Health and Vacation Fund (meeting minutes, financial reports, rules and regulations, benefits); the Organization Department (handmade fliers that were passed out in shops, lists of firms to organize as well as those that joined the manufacturer associations, reports, and the organizational campaign to unionize the entire cloak industry); the Price Adjustment Department (reports on rate increases, piece work settlements); and the Reefer Department (children's style of coat, reports from the children's coat department). Notable records involve the Overlapping Department. The correspondence references the encroachment of men's clothing establishments on the women's coat and suit industry. This production of ladies garments by men's garment manufacturers resulted from the new style of "mannish" suits for women.
There are files of correspondence and agreements with numerous Manufacturers Associations: the American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association, the Industrial Council of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, the Infants' and Childrens' Coat Association, Inc., and the Merchant Ladies Garment Association, Inc. Additionally, there were departments within the Joint Board that worked with the manufacturers. These included the Industrial Council Department and the Merchants-American Department. The Industrial Council Department of the Cloak Joint Board resolved complaints, settlements of prices, held investigations and shop meetings, handled and prepared union books, and were involved in union activities and publicity drives. They also managed all complaints with manufacturer associations, mainly the Industrial Council Association and American Association. The Merchants-American Department was similar in that it dealt with complaints, discharge of workers, payroll defaults, underpayment of wages, non-payment for overtime work, failure of shops to keep proper books, and visits and investigation of firms.
The general files of the Cloak Joint Board reflect the routine and administrative function of the Joint Board mainly from 1930 through the 1960s. Subjects include officer elections and installations, information on board members, speeches at the installation ceremonies, financial statements, assets and accounts, and informative reports created by the Research Department offering a look at production, earnings, and conditions in the industry through compiled studies. The records of the Joint Board Grievance Committee consists of cases before the committee, arranged by case number, with an overview of the grievance, individuals involved, and finals actions. The reports from the general manager to the Board of Directors of the Joint Board compiles the union's activities, and provides an overview of what was happening in the industry. The bulk of the collection is made up of correspondence, speeches, and even photographs of three of its managers, Israel Feinberg, Isidore Nagler, and Henoch Mendelsund. Israel Feinberg was manager of the Cloak Joint Board from 1920-1925, and then was reappointed in 1939 until his death in 1952. Isidore Nagler held the position of general manager from 1928-1939 and became manager again in 1952 until his death in 1959. Henoch Mendelsund was Nagler's assistant for years became the new manager of the Joint Board in 1959 and retired in 1973.
The Brooklyn Office of the Cloak Joint Board handled the shops and workers in Brooklyn, including charges and complaints, discharge cases, and reports from the office supervisors. Shop complaints from members and locals went to the Joint Board, the Grievance Committee and sometimes the Impartial Chairman. The Impartial Chairman of the Cloak and Suit Industry arbitrated disputes in the industry and the records contain hearings and cases as well as the decisions rendered. The National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry continued the work of the National Recovery Board to ensure that garments were made under fair working conditions. The records include correspondence, reports, negotiations, hand written notes, preparatory documents and research, proposals and demands.
The Cloak Out-of-Town Department was composed of locals that represented cloak workers not in New York City, but worked closely with the New York Cloak Joint Board and the collection contains meeting minutes and correspondence between managers and locals. There is also the correspondence with other Joint Boards across the country including the Los Angeles Joint Board and South Jersey-Philadelphia Joint Board. Locals affiliated with the Cloak Joint Board are contained in this collection, and in many instances their own as well: Cloak and Suit Tailors' Local 9 (5780/013; 5780/017; 5780/017P), Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union Local 10 (5780/001; 5780/008; 5780/011; 5780/012; 5780/094; 5780/131), Waterproof Garment Workers' Union Local 20, Blouse, Skirt and Sportswear Workers Union Local 23-25 (5780/059; 5780/059P; 5780/059Pubs; 5780/095), Skirt and Sportswear Workers' Union Local 23, Designers' Guild of Ladies' Apparel Local 30, Corset and Brassier Workers' Local 32, Cloak, Skirt and Dress Pressers Local 35 (5780/031), Italian Cloak, Suit and Skirt Makers Local 48 (5780/040), Buttonhole Makers Local 64, Examiners and Floor Workers Local 82 (5780/007), Office and Distribution Employees Local 99, Cloak and Dress Drivers' and Helpers Local 102, Snowsuits, Ski Wear, Leggings, Infants and Novelty Sportswear Local 105 (5780/053), United Cloak, Suit, Infants and Children's Coat Operators and Sample Makers Local 117 (5780/034), Knitgoods Workers Local 155 (5780/076; 5780/129).
Individual correspondents represented in the collection include: David Dubinsky; William Green; Averell Harriman; Sidney Hillman; Irving Howe; Jacob Javits; Fiorello LaGuardia; Herbert Lehman; Elias Lieberman; Jay Lovestone; George Meany; Marianne Moore; Jacob Potofsky; Nelson Rockefeller; Rose Schneiderman; Matthew Schoenwald; Mark Starr; Louis Stulberg; Norman Thomas; Gus Tyler; and Charles S. Zimmerman.
Organizations include: the AFL-CIO; the American Labor Party; Histadrut; the Jewish Daily Forward; the Jewish Labor Committee; the Liberal Party of New York; the National Recovery Administration; the Rand School of Social Science; and the Socialist Party.
The Second Series involves subject files arranged alphabetically for the Cloak Out-of-Town Department and include locals, educational programs and training seminars, and departments.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/032: ILGWU. New York Cloak Joint Board minutes 5780/041: ILGWU. New York Cloak Joint Board payroll analysis 5780/161: ILGWU. New York Cloak Joint Board. Advisory Commission on the Cloak, Suit, and Skirt Industry in New York records 5780/013: ILGWU. Local 9. Managers' correspondence 5780/017: ILGWU. Local 9. Executive Board and Grievance Committee minutes 5780/017: ILGWU. Local 9. Executive Board and Grievance Committee minutes 5780/001: ILGWU. Local 10 minutes 5780/008: ILGWU. Local 10 dues books 5780/011: ILGWU. Local 10. Managers' correspondence 5780/012: ILGWU. Local 10. Managers' correspondence 5780/094: ILGWU. Local 10 membership record books 5780/131: ILGWU. Local 10 records 5780/059: ILGWU. Local 23-25 records 5780/059: ILGWU. Local 23-25 records 5780/095: ILGWU. Local 23-25 records 5780/031: ILGWU. Local 35 records 5780/040: ILGWU. Local 48 records 5780/007: ILGWU. Local 82 minutes 5780/053: ILGWU. Local 105 records 5780/034: ILGWU. Local 117 minutes 5780/076: ILGWU. Local 132. Managers' correspondence 5780/129: ILGWU. Local 155 records
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Organizing -- New York (State) -- New York; Collective bargaining -- New York (State) -- New York; Economic assistance -- Israel; Health insurance -- New York (State) -- New York; International labor activities; Labor laws and legislation -- United States; Labor laws and legislation -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor union locals; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York -- Political activity; Pension trusts -- New York (State) -- New York; Wages -- Clothing workers -- New York (State) -- New York; Wages -- Clothing workers -- United States; Women's clothing industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Women's clothing industry -- United States; Working class -- Education -- New York (State) -- New York; Working class -- Education -- United States; New York (State) -- Politics and government -- 20th century; United States--Politics and government--20th century.; Dubinsky, David, 1892-1982.; Feinberg, Israel.; Green, William, 1872-1952.; Harriman, W. Averell(William Averell), 1891-1986.; Hillman, Sidney, 1887-1946.; Howe, Irving.; Javits, Jacob K.(Jacob Koppel), 1904-1986.; La Guardia, Fiorello H.(Fiorello Henry), 1882-1947.; Lehman, Herbert H.(Herbert Henry), 1878-1963.; Lieberman, Elias, b. 1888-; Lovestone, Jay.; Meany, George, 1894-1980; Mendelsund, Henoch.; Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972.; Nagler, Isadore.; Potofsky, Jacob S. (Jacob Samuel), 1894-1979; Rockefeller, Nelson A.(Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979.; Schneiderman, Rose, 1882-1972.; Schoenwald, Matthew.; Starr, Mark, 1894-; Stulberg, Louis, 1901-1977.; Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968.; Tyler, Gus.; Zimmerman, Charles S., 1896-1983.; AFL-CIO; American Labor Party; Histadrut ha-kelalit shel ha-'ovdim be-Erets-Yisra'el; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. New York Cloak Joint Board; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Cloak Out-of-Town Dept; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Cloak Out-of-Town Dept; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.); Liberal Party of New York State; Rand School of Social Science; Socialist Party (U.S.); Forṿerṭs (New York, N.Y.)
3708717
- Series I: New York Cloak Joint Board Subject Files, 1926-1973
  - A, 1940-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1a)
    Scope and Contents
    Incl. Arthur Altmeyer ltrs.
  - Asbestos [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1b)
    I.c.w. Irving J. Selikoff, M.D.; reports on hazards of asbestos in garments.
  - Asbestos [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1c)
  - Agency Account, 1952-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    I.c.w. David Dubinsky, Louis Stulberg & Harry Krugman and financial reports.
  - Agency Account, 1963-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Financial reports.
  - Agency Account, Bellevue (Nebraska) Bridge [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1966 (Box 1, Folder 4a)
    Legal briefs, ILGWU et al. vs Shields & Co. (suit pertaining to bridge).
  - Agency Account, Bellevue (Nebraska) Bridge [folder 2 of 2], 1950-1966 (Box 1, Folder 4b)
  - Agency Account, Tri-State Airport [folder 1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 5a)
  - Agency Account, Tri-State Airport [folder 2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 5b)
  - Authority [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6a)
    (Huntington, W. Va.) Corres., financial & annual reports.
  - Authority [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6b)
  - American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association, 1943-1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    I.c.w. Charles Sussman, Louis Goldspinner & Anthony Conticelli.
  - American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association, 1943-1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Corres. & statements during negotiations.
  - American Association for a Democratic Germany, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Labor, 1946-1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    I.c.w. William Green & George Meany (1952); corres. re Israel Feinberg's trip to Germany (1946); reports & resolutions.
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1955-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    I.c.w. Jay Lovestone & Louis Stulberg; resolutions.
  - B, 1940-1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    I.c.w. Boys' Town of Italy (Patrick Carroll-Abbing).
  - Bensonhurst Office, Cloak Joint Board, 1943-1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    I.c.w. E. Piccione & Max Carolinsky.
  - Brooklyn Office, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 1 of 4], 1951-1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Incl. reports by Anthony Cottone, Samuel Zeldin, John Denaro & Dante Di Biase.
  - Brooklyn Office, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 2 of 4], 1951-1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn Office, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 3 of 4], 1951-1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Brooklyn Office, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 4 of 4], 1951-1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Office, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 1 of 4], 1941-1950 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Corres. & reports, Anthony Cottone.
  - Brooklyn Office, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 2 of 4], 1941-1950 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Office, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 3 of 4], 1941-1950 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Office, Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 4 of 4], 1941-1950 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Brownsville Office, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1944-1951 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Corres. w. Alex J. Miller.
  - Bund (Jewish Workers Union of Poland), 1947-1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    I.c.w. Emanuel Scherer.
  - C, 1941-1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    I.c.w. Jesse Carpenter.
  - Celebration, 1910 Strike Anniversary, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Incl. Corres. re Carnegie Hall (NYC) meeting.
  - Celebration, 1910 Strike Anniversary, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Speeches & press releases.
  - Celebration, 1910 Strike Anniversary, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Photographs.
  - Celebration, 1910 Strike Anniversary, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Newspaper clippings.
  - Celebration, 1910 Strike Anniversary, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Incl. 50th anniversary journal, 1910 (Gerechtiqkeit) & programs.
  - Celebration, 25th Anniversary of David Dubinsky's Presidency, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Incl. circulars, notes & statements.
  - Celebration, 35th Anniversary of 1910 Cloakmakers' Strike, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Incl. speeches & releases.
  - Citizens' Union of the City of N.Y., 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - City of Hope (Los Angeles Sanatorium), 1949-1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    I.c.w. Ben Horowitz.
  - Cloak Control Department, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Saul Metz report.
  - Cloak Out-of-Town Department, 1965-1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Joint Council minutes.
  - Cloak Out-of-Town Dept, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    I.c.w. Louis Stulberg & Murray Edelstein.
  - Cloak Out-of-Town Dept, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    I.c.w. Irving Astrow, Mildred Lippman & William Ross.
  - Cloak Out-of-Town Dept, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    I.c.w. Irving Astrow & Louis Stulberg; reports on educational activities; memo on Mona Lisa Coat Co.; COT News (1966).
  - Cloak Out-of-Town Dept., 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    I.c.w. Irving Astrow & George Rubin.
  - Cloak Out-of-Town Dept., 1954-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    I.c.w. George Rubin & Morris Bagno.
  - Cloak Out-of-Town Dept., 1936-1948 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Incl. reports by George Rubin & Alex S. Miller.
  - Coat and Suit Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Incl. Hyman Libow reports.
  - Coat and Suit Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Coat and Suit Disabilities Benefits Fund, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Memo from Leon Hudes, with "Analysis of 1971 Correspondence Relating to Disability Benefits"
  - The Coat and Suit Survey. Women's Suits, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Feb. 1966. Analysis by Dr. Clara H. Friedman (director of research), Audits & Surveys Co., Inc.; also incl. second section of The Coat and Suit Survey (1964).
  - Collection Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd., 1965-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Memorandums.
  - Complaints from Workers, 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Complaints from Workers, 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Complaints from Workers, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Complaints from Workers, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Complaints from Workers, 1953-1957 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Complaints from Workers, 1940-1951 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Incl. undated ltrs.
  - Congress for Jewish Culture Central Yiddish Culture Organization (CYCO), Inc., 1948-1960 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Constitution, Jt. Bd. of the Cloak, Suit, Skirt, Dress and Reefer Makers' Unions of N.Y. and Vicinity, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Incl. amendments adopted Mar. 24, 1926.
  - Conventions, ILGWU, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Incl. Resolutions Comm. report.
  - Conventions, ILGWU, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Incl. Constitution Revision Comm. minutes (Mar. 19, 1968).
  - Conventions, ILGWU, 1965-1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Corres. & drafts of Constitutional Revision Comm.
  - Court Cases, 1953-1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    NLRB cases, briefs and memoranda, law suits.
  - D, 1940-1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Incl. Emma Dubinsky ltr. re "Testimonial Performance in Honor of Joseph Buloff & Luba Kadison."
  - Deborah Hospital (NYC), 1948-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - E, 1945-1962 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - East River Housing Corp. [folder 1 of 2], 1951-1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Incl. Corres. & minutes.
  - East River Housing Corp. [folder 2 of 2], 1951-1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Out-of-Town Dept., 1951-1959 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Sew n Sew (1956), a pub.; corres.
  - Eastern Region, 1966-1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Corres. & statements.
  - Epstein, Melech, 1947-1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Requests for financial aid for books on Jewish labor movement.
  - Evan-Picone, Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Corres. re negotiations & agreements, industrial problems, price lists; reports.
  - Evan-Picone, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - F-G, 1939-1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Fashion Capital of the World, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Incl. design contest.
  - Fashion Institute of Technology [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1972 (Box 8, Folder a)
    Robert F. Wagner (mayor) remarks at dedication of Isidore Nagler Hall (1962); textile pilot plant project; James Laver of Victoria and Albert Museum, London, speech (1965).
  - Fashion Institute of Technology [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1972 (Box 8, Folder 1b)
  - Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR), 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Newsletter, resolutions, printed material.
  - Feinberg, Israel, 1940-1952 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    I.c.w. Matthew Woll & ltr. to William Green re son, Basil.
  - Feinberg, Israel, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Corres. re "Labor Pains" & Calif. locals.
  - Feinberg, Israel, 1939-1950 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Incl. speeches & statements.
  - Feinberg, Israel, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Condolences on his death, newspaper articles.
  - Feinberg Memorial Fund, 1953-1957 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Incl. speeches at FIT lecture series.
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Complaint by Commission against Nat'l. Coat & Suit Recovery Bd., et al., for suppression of competition.
  - Form Letters, 1940-1962 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Incl. press releases & broadsides (Union & non-Union).
  - Freeland League, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - General Executive Board, 1942-1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Corres. & reports of the gen'l. mgr.
  - GEB, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Report of I. Nagler re jurisdictional questions bet. Locals 23 & 105.
  - Government Work, 1949-1951 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Lists of shops available for gov't orders during Korean War.
  - Grievance and Appeal Committee. Cloak Jt. Bd., 1942-1959 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Minutes & reports.
  - Guaranteed Holidays, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Re payment to members for paid holidays.
  - H, 1948-1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    I.c.w. Hannah Haskel, Hebrew Sheltering & Immigrant Aid Society, Roy Helfgott & Irving Howe; Averell Harriman ltr.
  - Handmacher and Vogel, Inc., 1961-1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Master agreement (May 1967) & corres.
  - Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York (HIP), 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Health and Vacation Fund, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Health and Vacation Fund, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Health and Vacation Fund, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1946-1954 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Minutes, rules & regulations, corres.
  - Health and Welfare Fund, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1965-1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Corres., Blue Cross Group Contract (1968); estimated income and expenses.
  - Health and Welfare Fund, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Minutes of Bd. of Trustees (1964-67); form ltrs.; comparison of benefits before and after July 1967.
  - Health and Welfare Fund, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Rules and Regulations.
  - Health and Welfare Fund, Cloak Jt. Bd., 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Pamphlets to members, corres.
  - High School of Fashion Industries, 1950-1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    I.c.w. Central High School of Needle Trades.
  - Home and Hospital of the Daughters of Jacob, 1954-1959 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Housing, 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Proposals re retired members.
  - I, 1953-1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Impartial Chairmen [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Decisions, statements & corres.
  - Impartial Chairmen [folder 2 of 2], 1947-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Impartial Chairmen [folder 1 of 2], 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1a)
    Hearings re Union demand for a wage readjustment, statements.
  - Impartial Chairmen [folder 2 of 2], 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1b)
  - Impartial Chairmen, 1932-1945 (Box 11, Folder 1c)
  - Industrial Council of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, Inc. [folder 1 of 3], 1945-1968 (Box 11, Folder 2a)
    I.c.w. Samuel Klein, Bertram Reinitz; Union notices to employers re collective negotiations.
  - Industrial Council of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, Inc. [folder 2 of 3], 1945-1968 (Box 11, Folder 2b)
  - Industrial Council of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, Inc. [folder 3 of 3], 1945-1968 (Box 11, Folder 2c)
  - Industrial Council Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd., 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Corres. & reports by Alex S. Miller & Hyman Libow.
  - Industrial Council Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 1 of 3], 1945-1955 (Box 12, Folder 1a)
    Corres. & reports by Morris Feinberg, N. Hines & Alex S. Miller.
  - Industrial Council Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 2 of 3], 1945-1955 (Box 12, Folder 1b)
  - Industrial Council Dept., Cloak Jt. Bd. [folder 3 of 3], 1945-1955 (Box 12, Folder 1c)
  - Infants' and Children's Coat Association, Inc. [folder 1 of 3], 1945-1973 (Box 12, Folder 2a)
    I.c.w. Joseph L. Rubin & Charles Baker.
  - Infants' and Children's Coat Association, Inc. [folder 2 of 3], 1945-1973 (Box 12, Folder 2b)
  - Infants' and Children's Coat Association, Inc. [folder 3 of 3], 1945-1973 (Box 12, Folder 2c)
  - International Labour Organization [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1a)
    Corres., speeches and reports re Textiles. Committee meeting in Geneva; George Meany ltr.; Henoch Mendelsund, Workers' Delegate to ILO.
  - International Labour Organization [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1b)
  - International Labour Organization, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 1c)
    I.c.w. Pinhas Lavon; trip abroad by Isidore Nagler, incl. meeting of ILO as Advisor to Workers' Delegate.
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union [folder 1 of 2], 1940-1971 (Box 13, Folder 2a)
    I.c.w. David Dubinsky & Louis Stulberg; Dubinsky speech (n.d.).
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union [folder 2 of 2], 1940-1971 (Box 13, Folder 2b)
  - ILGWU. Campaign Committees, 1960-1972 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    I.c.w. Evelyn Dubrow, Louis Stulberg; form ltrs.
  - ILGWU. Campaign Committees, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Leaflets & form ltrs
  - ILGWU. Education Dept., 1948-1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    I.c.w. Hark Starr, Gus Tyler, Jasper Peyton; ltr. from James T. Farrell; talk by Henoch Mendelsund (executive secretary). Local 9, to Officers' Qualification Courses (Sept. 1952).